Now let's work on the HTML for our hero
では、ヒーローの HTML に取り組みましょう
image. I'm going to lead off with a
画像。 私はで始めるつもりです
division.
分割。
This division is going to have a class
この部門にはクラスがあります
and I'm just going to make up the word
そして、私はただ言葉を作るつもりです
'hero' because it seems appropriate.
「ヒーロー」は適切だと思われるためです。
Inside that, we're going to have a
その中には、
picture tag.
絵札。
The picture tag is going to begin
絵札がはじまります
with a source.
ソース付き。
The source is going to have a source set
ソースにはソースセットがあります
attribute.
属性。
I'll fill that out in a second. It
すぐに記入します。 それ
also has a media query.
メディアクエリもあります。
Inside here we're going to use a
ここでは、
max-width.
最大幅。
The width we'll use for this first
この最初に使用する幅
source is the width of our smallest
ソースは私たちの最小の幅です
image which you'll you will remember is
あなたが思い出すであろうイメージは
500 pixels.
500 ピクセル。
The second source is just like the first
2 番目のソースは最初のソースと同じです
one except that the media query now
メディアクエリを除いて1つ
matches the medium image width.
中間の画像幅に一致します。
Now we're ready for a standard
これで標準の準備が整いました
image tag.
イメージタグ。
Images have sources.
画像にはソースがあります。
In this particular case, the source is
この特定のケースでは、ソースは
the large image.
大きな画像。
It has an alt and I'll just call this
それにはaltがあり、これを呼び出すだけです
hero.
ヒーロー。
Then we're going to have a width
次に、幅を設定します
equals...
等しい...
and a height equals...
そして高さが等しい...
Then we'll finish it off.
それでは仕上げていきます。
So what should the width and height be
では、幅と高さはどうあるべきか
considering that we had three different
私たちが3つの異なるものを持っていたことを考えると
images,
画像、
and three different widths and heights.
3 つの異なる幅と高さ。
Well, actually since 2019 the width and
まあ、実際には2019年から幅と
height are a ratio they are not related
高さは関係のない比率です
to the pixel width and height of the
ピクセルの幅と高さに
source image so you could put any one of
ソース画像なので、次のいずれかを配置できます
the three combinations in here. Let's
この3つの組み合わせ。 しましょう
go ahead and put 500
先に進んで500を入れてください
and 250.
そして250。
Or, we could just as easily do 50 by 25
または、50 x 25 を同じように簡単に行うこともできます。
that's still a two by one ratio.
それはまだ2対1の比率です。
I'm going to copy this path,
このパスをコピーします。
and I'll paste it up here, and change the
ここに貼り付けて
word 'large'
「大きい」という言葉
to 'small'
「小さい」に
For the second one
2つ目は
we'll use 'medium'.
「中」を使用します。
You can see over here is a very small
ここは非常に小さいことがわかります
preview...
プレビュー...
Let me go ahead and use the larger values.
先に進み、より大きな値を使用しましょう。
There we go, you can see a little bit better.
ほら、もう少しよく見えるはずです。
So there's this small one,
だから、この小さなものがあります。
because our browser is narrower than a
私たちのブラウザは
maximum width of 500. Once we go a little
最大幅 500。少し進んだら
bit wider, it now jumps to the medium image.
少し広くなり、中間の画像にジャンプします。
What's happening here is it's actually
ここで起きていることは実際に
taking this source set path and it's
このソース セット パスを取得すると、
replacing this srcset down here on line
この srcset をオンラインで置き換えます
17. When we get to medium it takes the
17. ミディアムになると、
medium srcset and uses that as the
medium srcset を作成し、それを
path for the image source.
画像ソースのパス。
So here we have the small image...
ここに小さな画像があります...
the medium image... and the large image.
中画像…そして大画像。
Now it's not scaling with the page but
今はページに合わせてスケーリングしていませんが、
it is changing based on the width of my
それは私の幅に基づいて変化しています
browser.
ブラウザ。